[Music]
as the leader of a small to medium-sized
business you wear a lot of hats
Visionary
Creator motivator and everything in
between you know your core business your
customers and your competition whether
in times of growth or uncertainty when
it comes to being at the leading edge of
your industry one constant Remains the
ability to be agile and resilient to
change and my Microsoft Dynamics 365
business Central provides the tools you
need to thrive to stay competitive in a
changing Marketplace successful
businesses have moved to the cloud with
Dynamics 365 business
Central now more than ever small and
medium businesses are looking to both
grow their business and become more
efficient this means adopting new tools
and processes that will help them Reach
new heights this will include AI which
can help people with repetitive tasks
assist them on on a daily basis and
ultimately improve job satisfaction
business Central empowers you to do all
of this and more in a comprehensive
all-in-one business application Suite
this includes managing your Finance your
service your sales and operations
providing a holistic view of your
company and your data and it's available
in over 130 countries ensuring business
Central is available wherever you are
and wherever your customers are with
business Central you can maximize your
productivity using the Microsoft 365
Suite this includes business
intelligence with a Power Platform
letting you see your data in entirely
new ways this will include the Microsoft
Dynamics 365 co-pilot unleashing
productivity and letting people do
things that they never thought they
could do before it's all built on top of
azure with the reliability the security
and compliance that comes with it and of
course the Microsoft partner network has
experts around the world that know your
company and know your industry and can
support you wherever you are ultimately
business Central allows teams to adapt
faster work smarter and perform better
using business Central but also by using
Barbi we can better manage our inventory
levels as a result every month is our
best selling month so it keeps on
growing just because we can keep the
focus on getting our products into the
market and delivering the right products
to the right consumer business Central
enables you to confidently move to the
cloud and adapt faster to a rapidly
changing
environment Empower your employees to
work smarter by leveraging the power of
AI optimizing productivity with
automated workflows and taking advantage
of the interoperability with Microsoft
365 and
teams and finally enable your
organization to perform better with
realtime insights into cash flow and
visibility into key performance metrics
available at any time wherever you
choose to work in a landscape that's
constantly evolving the tools to evolve
with it are more important than ever
always be ready for what's next and
unlock Limitless possibilities with
Microsoft Dynamics 365 business
Central